module.exports = [
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: 'Which friend found a naked picture of Monica?',
    answer: 'Joey',
    options: ['Joey', 'Chandler', 'Ross']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `Which of the following is Ross obsessed with: collecting stamps, dinosaurs, or photography?`,
    answer: 'Dinosaurs',
    options: ['Dinosaurs', 'Stamps', 'Photography']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `Which Friend did not go to high school?`,
    answer: 'Phoebe',
    options: ['Phoebe', 'Joey', 'Ross']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `Which Friend was a bell ringer for the Salvation Army?`,
    answer: 'Phoebe',
    options: ['Phoebe', 'Monica', 'Rachel']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `Which of the guys once bought a pair of leather pants?`,
    answer: 'Ross',
    options: ['Ross', 'Chandler', 'Joey']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `While in London, which member of the royal family did Joey meet?`,
    answer: 'Sarah Ferguson, The Duchess of York',
    options: ['Sarah Ferguson, The Duchess of York', 'Meghan Markle, The Duches of Sussex', 'William, Prince of Wales']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `What kinds of animals are Chandler and Joey's pets?`,
    answer: 'A chick (chicken) and a duck',
    options: ['A chick (chicken) and a duck', 'Marcel the monkey', 'Smelly Cat']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `Which Friend is one-half Scottish?`,
    answer: 'Chandler',
    options: ['Chandler', 'Joey', 'Ross']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `What body anomaly did Chandler have removed?`,
    answer: 'His nubbin (third nipple)',
    options: ['His nubbin (third nipple)', 'Mole on buttcheek', 'Hernia']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `What part of Chandler's body did a knife dropped by Monica sever?`,
    answer: 'His pinky toe',
    options: ['His pinky tow', 'His nubbin (third nipple)', 'His big toe']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `Unable to afford an entire set of encyclopedias, Joey bought only what volume?`,
    answer: `The 'V' Volume`,
    options: [`The 'V' Volume`, `The 'J' Volume`, `The 'T' Volume`]
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `What's Joey's favorite professional basketball team?`,
    answer: 'The New York Knicks',
    options: ['The New York Knicks', 'The Los Angeles Lakers', 'The Space Jam Tunes']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `What do Monica and Rachel do to finally get their apartment back from the guys?`,
    answer: 'They kiss',
    options: ['They kiss', 'They win a bet', 'They steal it']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `Chandler was trapped in an ATM vestibule with what supermodel?`,
    answer: 'Jill Goodacre',
    options: ['Jill Goodacre', 'Yasmine Bleeth', 'Fabio']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `Which animal ate Rachel's face cream?`,
    answer: 'The duck',
    options: ['The duck', 'The chicken', 'Marcel the monkey']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `One of Joey's first big breaks was starring in a movie as Al Pacino's what?`,
    answer: 'Butt Double',
    options: ['Butt Double', 'Stuntman', 'Twin']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `What's the name of Phoebe's song about a feline?`,
    answer: 'Smelly Cat',
    options: ['Smelly Cat', 'Duck Duck Goose', 'Three Little Birds']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `Which Friend has freakishly small feet?`,
    answer: 'Joey',
    options: ['Joey', 'Chandler', 'Ross']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `Which Friend helped from the "I Hate Rachel Green Club?"`,
    answer: 'Ross',
    options: ['Ross', 'Chandler', 'Joey']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `What is Phoebe's fake name?`,
    answer: 'Regina Phalange',
    options: ['Regina Phalange', 'Princess Consuela Banana Hammock', 'Ursula']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `How does Monica eat Tic Tacs?`,
    answer: 'In even numbers',
    options: ['In even numbers', 'Over the sink', 'With a plate']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `Which Friend likes mashed potato with lumps?`,
    answer: 'Ross',
    options: ['Ross', 'Chandler', 'Joey']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `Which Friend is freaked out by people touching their own eye?`,
    answer: 'Rachel',
    options: ['Rachel', 'Monica', 'Phoebe']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `Which friend is most likely to eat macaroni and cheese at Thanksgiving?`,
    answer: 'Chandler',
    options: ['Chandler', 'Ross', 'Joey']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `What kind of toy does Chandler like to take baths with?`,
    answer: 'A toy battleship',
    options: ['A toy battleship', 'A rubber ducky', 'Monica doll']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `What fact about Christmas trees horrifies Phoebe?`,
    answer: `The trees that don't sell are destroyed`,
    options: [`The trees that don't sell are destroyed`, 'That they are leafy', 'Smelly trees are like smelly cat']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `Joey's soap opera character got what kind of transplant?`,
    answer: 'A brain transplant',
    options: ['A brain transplant', 'A penis transplant', 'A hair transplant']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `Which Friend took part in a fertility study?`,
    answer: 'Joey',
    options: ['Joey', 'Chandler', 'Ross']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `What does Phoebe claim happen every time she goes to the dentist?`,
    answer: 'Someone dies',
    options: ['Someone dies', 'She gets her teeth cleaned', 'Smelly cat gets clean']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `What did Rachel incorrectly say that Chandler's job was?`,
    answer: 'Transponster',
    options: ['Transponster', 'Actor', 'Professor']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `What is Monica's favorite drink?`,
    answer: 'Scotch on the rocks with a twist',
    options: ['Scotch on the rocks with a twist', 'Margarita', 'Red Wine']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `Name one of the two instruments we see Ross play on Friends?`,
    answer: 'Bagpipes and the keyboard',
    options: ['Bagpipes and the keyboard', 'Drums', 'Guitar']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `You can make Joey cry just by talking about what movie?`,
    answer: 'Titanic',
    options: ['Titanic', 'Bambi', 'Weekend at Bernies']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `Which Friend makes sex noises when getting massages?`,
    answer: 'Monica',
    options: ['Monica', 'Phoebe', 'Rachel']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `What's Chandler's middle name?`,
    answer: 'Muriel',
    options: ['Muriel', 'Bing', 'Clint']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `What was the name of Joey's favorite chair?`,
    answer: 'Rosita',
    options: ['Rosita', 'Hugsy', 'Stevie']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `What kind of fruit is Ross allergic to?`,
    answer: 'Kiwi',
    options: ['Kiwi', 'Apple', 'Grapes']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `What's the name of Joey's stuffed penguin pal?`,
    answer: 'Hugsy',
    options: ['Hugsy', 'Pikachu', 'Marcel']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `What fake name does Joey sometimes use?`,
    answer: 'Ken Adams',
    options: ['Ken Adams', 'Matt Leblanc', 'Drake Ramoray']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `What does it mean when Monica is wearing her "old lady" underpants?` ,
    answer: `It's laundry day`,
    options: [`it's laundry day`, `She's getting ready for a date`, 'She broke up with Dr. Burt']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `What does Rachel claim is her favorite movie?`,
    answer: 'Dangerous Liaisons',
    options: ['Dangerous Liaisons', 'Weekend at Bernies', 'Along came Polly']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `What is the name of Joey's character on Days of Our Lives?`,
    answer: 'Dr. Drake Ramoray',
    options: ['Dr. Drake Ramoray', 'Ken Adams', 'Stryker Ramoray']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    qustion: `What was Ross's monkey's name?`,
    answer: 'Marcel',
    options: ['Marcel', 'George', 'King Kong']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `Where is the weirdest place Joey ever fooled around?`,
    answer: `New York Public Library's women's room`,
    options: [`New York Public Library's women's room`, 'Foot of the bed', 'Disney World']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `A pizza was accidentally delivered to the girls. It was meant for whom?`,
    answer: 'George Stephanopoulos',
    options: ['George Stephanopoulas', 'Ugly naked guy', 'Chandler and Joey']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `What is Joey's favorite food?`,
    answer: 'Sandwiches',
    options: ['Sandwiches', 'CheeseCake', 'Two Pizzas']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `What does Ross refer to the middle piece of bread as in his sandwich?`,
    answer: 'The Moist Maker',
    options: ['The Moist Maker', 'Unagi', 'Marcel']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `When Ross moves in with Chandler and Joey, what song does he put on their answering machine?`,
    answer: 'We Will Rock You',
    options: ['We Will Rock You', 'Smelly Cat', 'Jurassic Park theme']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `What's the name of the chapel where Ross and Rachel exchange drunken vows?`,
    answer: 'A Little White Chapel',
    options: ['A Little White Chapel', 'We were on a Break Chapel', 'The One with the Chapel']
  },
  {
    category: 'PET PEEVES',
    question: `Phoebe found what in a can of soda?`,
    answer: 'A thumb',
    options: ['A thumb', 'Ice', 'Meat']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `When was the last time Ross saw Will?`,
    answer: `Lance Davis' graduation party`,
    options: [`Lance Davis' graduation party`, 'After Brad cheated on Jennifer', 'Friends Reunion']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `Which one of the guys once wore a goatee?`,
    answer: 'Chandler',
    options: ['Chandler', 'Joey', 'Ross']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `What was the name of Ross and Monica's childhood dog?`,
    answer: 'Chi Chi',
    options: ['Chi Chi', 'Marcel', 'Rufus']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `What was the name of Monica's pretend bakery she "started" with her Easy Bake Oven?`,
    answer: `Easy Monica's Bakery`,
    options: [`Easy Monica's Bakery`, 'Big Fat Bakery', `Little Mama's Bakery`]
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `What movie did Ross camp out to see as a teenager?`,
    answer: 'Star Wars Return of the Jedi',
    options: ['Star Wars Return of the Jedi', 'Jurassic Park', 'Along came Polly']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `Which friend mugged Ross when he was a kid?`,
    answer: 'Phoebe',
    options: ['Phoebe', 'Chandler', 'Joey']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `Whose mom was a drug dealer?`,
    answer: 'Phoebe',
    options: ['Phoebe', 'Monica', 'Rachel']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `What was the playground nickname of the character played by Julia Roberts?`,
    answer: 'Susie Underpants',
    options: ['Susie Underpants', 'Vivian Ward', 'Erin Brockovich']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `What is the name of the high school Ross, Monica and Rachel graduated from?`,
    answer: 'Lincoln High School',
    options: ['Lincoln High School', 'Top Secret School of Spies', 'Central Perk High School']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `Joey claims he weighed how much when he was born?`,
    answer: '27 pounds',
    options: ['27 pounds', '1 ton', '7 ounces']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `What did Rachel's sorority sister call her?`,
    answer: 'Ray Ray Green',
    options: ['Ray Ray Green', 'Regina Flangie', 'Jennifer Aniston']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `Ross' crush on Rachel began when he was in what grade?`,
    answer: 'Ninth grade',
    options: ['Ninth grade', 'Third grade', 'Sixth grade']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `Which Friend was a high school prom queen?`,
    answer: 'Rachel',
    options: ['Rachel', 'Monica', 'Phoebe']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `Who bought Chandler his first condoms?`,
    answer: 'His mom',
    options: ['His mom', 'Ross', 'His dad']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `Which Friend owned the album, It's Not Easy Being Green, as a child?`,
    answer: 'Monica',
    options: ['Monica', 'Rachel', 'Phoebe']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `As a child, whose poster did Monica kiss every night before going to sleep?`,
    answer: 'Kermit the Frog',
    options: ['Kermit the Frog', 'Nsync', 'Brad Pitt']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `When Ross was in college, where did he go for Spring Break?`,
    answer: 'Egypt',
    options: ['Egypt', 'Jurassic Park', 'London']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `As a child, Ross had a T-shirt that said what?`,
    answer: 'Tyrannosaurus Ross',
    options: ['Tyrannosaurus Ross', 'I hate Monica', 'Rossatron']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `What news did Rachel spill about Ross and the 50-year-old librarian?`,
    answer: 'That they made out',
    options: ['That they made out', 'That they were on a break', 'That he rented a book']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `What name was on Ross' fake ID in college?`,
    answer: 'Clifford Alverez',
    options: ['Clifford Alverez', 'Ken Adams', 'David Schwimmer']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `What name was on Chandler's fake ID in college?`,
    answer: 'Rowland Cheng',
    options: ['Rowland Cheng', 'Chananler Bong', 'Clint']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `What was the name of Rachel's sorority?`,
    answer: 'Kappa Kappa Delta',
    options: ['Kappa Kappa Delta', 'Emma', 'Unagi']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `What was the name of Rachel's childhood nanny?`,
    answer: 'Mrs. K',
    options: ['Mrs. K', 'Mannie', 'Rosita']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `During which Geller Bowl did Monica break Ross' nose?`,
    answer: 'Geller Bowl VI',
    options: ['Geller Bowl VI', 'Geller Bowl Pilot', 'Geller Bowl 7']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `Where was the strangest place Ross ever fooled around?`,
    answer: `The It's a Small World ride at Disneyland`,
    options: [`The It's a Small World ride at Disneyland`, 'Foot of the Bed', 'Public Library']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `Whose father bought them a boat at age 15?`,
    answer: 'Rachel',
    options: ['Rachel', 'Monica', 'Phoebe']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `Which of the Friends could not tell time until they were 13?`,
    answer: 'Monica',
    options: ['Monica', 'Rachel', 'Phoebe']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `Which Friend won a Vanilla Ice lookalike contest?`,
    answer: 'Chandler',
    options: ['Chandler', 'Joey', 'Ross']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `Which of the guys wore leg warmers in college?`,
    answer: 'Ross',
    options: ['Ross', 'Chandler', 'Joey']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `Which Friend claimed to have skipped fourth grade?`,
    answer: 'Ross',
    options: ['Ross', 'Chandler', 'Joey']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `What was Chandler's favorite childhood book?`,
    answer: 'The Velveteen Rabbit',
    options: ['The Velveteen Rabbit', 'Green Eggs and Ham', 'Dr. Seuss']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `What toy was glued to top of the Geller Cup?`,
    answer: 'A troll doll',
    options: ['A troll doll', 'A barbie doll', 'G.I. Joe']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `Because Ross and Rachel's break up reminds him of his parents' divorce, what does Chandler start doing?`,
    answer: 'Smoking',
    options: ['Smoking', 'Telling jokes', 'drinking']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `What did Ross wear the night he was going to take Rachel to the prom?`,
    answer: `His dad's tuxedo`,
    options: [`His dad's tuxedo`, 'Leather pants', `All Chandler's clothes`]
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `What was the coffee house before it became a coffee house?`,
    answer: 'A bar',
    options: ['A bar', 'A comedy club', 'A strip club']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `What happened the first time Monica tried to ride a bike?`,
    answer: 'The bike bent',
    options: ['The bike bent', 'She broke a leg', 'She lost weight']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `What disturbing footage was at the end of the prom video tape?`,
    answer: `Monica and Ross's parents fooling around`,
    options: [`Monica and Ross's parents fooling around`, 'Ross and Rachel fooling around', 'Chandler singing']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `What part of her anatomy has Rachel had plastic surgery on?`,
    answer: 'Her nose',
    options: ['Her nose', 'Her breasts', 'Her butt']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `When she was a teenager, who told Monica she should be a chef?`,
    answer: 'Chandler',
    options: ['Chandler', 'Ross', 'Rachel']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `Monica's prom date saw what movie 317 times?`,
    answer: 'Star Wars',
    options: ['Star Wars', 'Indiana Jones', 'Titanic']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `Which of the Friends were college roommates?`,
    answer: 'Ross and Chandler',
    options: ['Ross and Chandler', 'Monica and Rachel', 'Joey and Phoebe']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `Who did Chandler's dad leave Chandler's mom for?`,
    answer: 'The house boy',
    options: ['The house boy', 'The pool boy', 'The mail man']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `What was Monica's nickname on her high school field hockey team?`,
    answer: 'Big Fat Goalie',
    options: ['Big Fat Goalie', 'Bit Fattie', 'Fluffy']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `What song did Ross want to sing to Rachel when he came home from college for Thanksgiving?`,
    answer: 'Emotional Knapsack',
    options: ['Emotional Knapsack', 'We Will Rock You', 'All I Ever Wanted']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `What children's show sent Phoebe a keychain after her mother committed suicide?`,
    anwer: 'Sesame Street',
    options: ['Sesame Street', 'Barnie', `Blue's Clues`]
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `Name Rachel's beloved childhood dog`,
    answer: 'LaPooh',
    options: ['LaPooh', 'Chi Chi', 'Snoopy']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `Which Friend once got their head stuck in a raw turkey?`,
    answer: 'Joey',
    options: ['Joey', 'Chandler', 'Ross']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `How did Rachel's beloved childhood dog bite the dust?`,
    answer: `Hit by an ice cream truck and dragged 19 blocks`,
    options: ['Hit by an ice cream truck and dragged 19 blocks', 'Phoebe ran over it', 'Heart Worms']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `Which Friend rushed the stage at the Wham concert?`,
    answer: 'Chandler',
    options: ['Chandler', 'Joey', 'Ross']
  },
  {
    category: 'ANCIENT HISTORY',
    question: `Name one of the two teams Carol played on in college`,
    answer: 'Golf of LaCrosse',
    options: ['Golf of LaCrosse', 'Volley Ball', 'Soft Ball']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: 'What was the name of the health inspector Phoebe dated?',
    answer: 'Larry',
    options: ['Larry', 'Gadget', 'Gunther']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What is Phoebe's twin sister's name?`,
    answer: 'Ursula',
    options: ['Ursula', 'Regina', 'Lisa']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What was the name of the woman Rachel's ex-fiance married?`,
    answer: 'Mindy',
    options: ['Mindy', 'Angelina', 'Emma']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What is Rachel's ex-fiance's name?`,
    answer: 'Barry',
    options: ['Barry', 'Ross', 'Brad']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `Name one of Phoebe's triplets`,
    answer: 'Chandler, Lesie or Frank Jr. Jr',
    options: ['Chandler, Lesie or Frank Jr. Jr', 'Joey, Emma, Frank Sr. Sr', 'Ken, Adams, Ursula']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `When Rachel dated Joshua, he had a phobia of what?`,
    answer: 'Farm birds',
    options: ['Farm birds', 'Spiders', 'Heights']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What was the name of Ross's second ex-wife?`,
    answer: 'Emily',
    options: ['Emily', 'Rachel', 'Carol']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What did Ross and Rachel name their baby?`,
    answer: 'Emma',
    options: ['Emma', 'Grace', 'Leslie']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What's Phoebe's father's name?`,
    answer: 'Frank',
    options: ['Frank', 'Jack', 'Ken']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What was the name of the police officer Phoebe dated?`,
    answer: 'Gary',
    options: ['Gary', 'Mike', 'Marcus']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `How many sisters does Joey have?`,
    answer: 'Seven',
    options: ['Seven', 'Six', 'Eight']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `Who threw water balloons at Ross when he broke up with her?`,
    answer: 'Elizabeth',
    options: ['Elizabeth', 'Rachel', 'Janice']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What was the name of the guy Rachel dated who looked a lot like Ross?`,
    answer: 'Russ',
    options: ['Russ', 'Joshua', 'Anthony']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What was the name of the soap star Rachel dated?`,
    answer: 'Kash',
    options: ['Kash', 'Joey', 'Ross']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `Who did Rachel go out with on her first date since Ross?`,
    answer: 'Mark',
    options: ['Mark', 'Brad', 'Barry']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `How long had Ross and Carol been together?`,
    answer: 'Seven years',
    options: ['Seven years', 'Six years', 'Eight years']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `Who was the last Friend to know about Monica and Chandler dating?`,
    answer: 'Ross',
    options: ['Ross', 'Joey', 'Rachel']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `Which Friend slept with Rachel's boss, Joanna?`,
    answer: 'Chandler',
    options: ['Chandler', 'Ross', 'Joey']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `How old was Ross and Monica's cousin Cassie when she visited them?`,
    answer: '25',
    options: ['25', '30', '21']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What airport did Ross go to, to try and stop Rachel from moving?`,
    answer: 'JFK',
    options: ['JFK', 'LaGuardia', 'Newark']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What was Phoebe's birth mother's name?`,
    answer: 'Phoebe',
    options: ['Phoebe', 'Monica', 'Rachel']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What is the name of Chandler's father's Las Vegas revue?`,
    answer: 'Viva Las Gaygas',
    options: ['Viva Las Gaygas', 'Viva La Vida Loca', 'Viva Mi Culo']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `Who is Ben's godfather?`,
    answer: 'Chandler',
    options: ['Chandler', 'Ross', 'Joey']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What was the name of Phoebe's psychiatrist boyfriend?`,
    answer: 'Roger',
    options: ['Roger', 'Gary', 'David']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What was the name of the woman who raised Phoebe?`,
    answer: 'Lily',
    options: ['Lily', 'Phoebe', 'Regina']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What's Phoebe's grandmother's name?`,
    answer: 'Francis',
    options: ['Francis', 'Emily', 'Elizabeth']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What was Phoebe doing the first time she saw David?`,
    answer: 'Singing on stage at the coffeehouse',
    options: ['Singing on stage at the coffeehouse', 'Working at the massage parlor', 'Eating dinner with Joey']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What was the name of the girl Joey and Ross dated at the same time?`,
    answer: 'Kristin',
    options: ['Kristin', 'Janice', 'Rachel']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `Why did Monica and Richard break up?`,
    answer: `Richard didn't want kids`,
    options: [`Richard didn't want kids`, 'Richard was too old', 'Richard called her a twinky']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What was Janice's nickname for Chandler`,
    answer: 'Bingaling',
    options: ['Bingaling', 'Mr. Biget', 'The Chan Man']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `Which sister of Joey's asks Rachel for single mom advice?`,
    answer: 'Dina',
    options: ['Dina', 'Mary Angela', 'Gina']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `Where did Ross meet Mona?`,
    answer: `Chandler and Monica's wedding`,
    options: [`Chandler and Monica's wedding`, 'At the University', 'The coffeehouse']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `Who teaches Ben all about practical jokes?`,
    answer: 'Rachel',
    options: ['Rachel', 'Monica', 'Phoebe']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `Who was the female paleontologist Ross had to show around town?`,
    answer: 'Charlie Weaver',
    options: ['Charlie Weaver', 'Regina Flangi', 'Emily Waltham']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `Who was Rachel's Italian lover?`,
    answer: 'Paolo',
    options: ['Paolo', 'Pauli', 'Vinny']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `Which Friend kissed Chandler's mom?`,
    answer: 'Ross',
    options: ['Ross', 'Joey', 'Rachel']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What job does Chandler's mom do?`,
    answer: 'Romance novelist',
    options: ['Romance novelist', 'Playmate', 'Las Vegas performer']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `A man at Ross and Emily's wedding mistook Monica for which family member?`,
    answer: `Ross's mother`,
    options: [`Ross's mother`, `Joey's mother`, `Chandler's mother`]
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `Phoebe's scientist boyfriend moved to this city?`,
    answer: 'Minsk',
    options: ['Minsk', 'Yeman', 'Rome']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `How many times has Ross been married?`,
    answer: 'Three',
    options: ['Three', 'Four', 'Two']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What did Aunt Silvia leave Monica?`,
    answer: 'A doll house',
    options: ['A doll house', 'A painting', 'Easy bake oven']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `Who threw Ross' bachelor party?`,
    answer: 'Joey',
    options: ['Joey', 'Chandler', 'Ben']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `Name Ross's ex-wife's life partner`,
    answer: 'Susan',
    options: ['Susan', 'Regina', 'Ursula']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What faux pas does Ross make during his vows to Emily?`,
    answer: `He says Rachel's name`,
    options: [`He says Rachel's name`, `He says 'I don't'`, 'He runs away']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What did Monica's boyfriend, Richard, do for work?`,
    answer: 'Opthamologist',
    options: ['Opthamologist', 'Police Officer', 'Actor']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What was the name of Chandler's on-again, off-again girlfriend?`,
    answer: 'Janice',
    options: ['Janice', 'Kathy', 'Monica']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `Prior to Phoebe, who lived in Phoebe's apartment?`,
    answer: `Phoebe's grandmother`,
    options: [`Phoebe's grandmother`, 'Monica', 'Rachel']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What are and Monica's parents' names?`,
    answer: 'Jack and Judy Geller',
    options: ['Jack and Judy Geller', 'Frank and Francis Geller', 'Luke and Leia Geller']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What actual object was blamed for outing Monica and Chandler to Joey?`,
    answer: 'An eyelash curler',
    options: ['An eyelash curler', 'Earring', 'Necklace']
  },
  {
    category: `IT'S ALL RELATIVE`,
    question: `What is the occupation of Rachel's ex-fiance?`,
    answer: 'Dentist',
    options: ['Dentist', 'Professor', 'Actor']
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: `On Ross' "Pros and Cons" list, what was Julie's one "con?"`,
    answer: `She's not Rachel`,
    options: [`She's not Rachel`, `She's ugly`, `Doesn't believe in evolution`],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: `What is Joey's favorite pick up line?`,
    answer: `How you doin'`,
    options: [`How you doin'`, 'I went backpacking across Western Europe', 'Hey you'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'Joey gave Chandler a bracelet that was engraved with what phrase?',
    answer: 'To My Best Bud',
    options: ['To My Best Bud', 'My Bestfriend', 'Best Buddies'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: `What was Rachel referring to when she said Ross "good at the stuff?"`,
    answer: 'Sex',
    options: ['Sex', 'Kissing', 'Massages'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'The official title of every Friends episode begins with which two words?',
    answer: 'The One...',
    options: ['The One...', 'Episode where...', `Here's where...`],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'What does the tiny t-shirt that Ross puts on say?',
    answer: 'Frankie Says Relax',
    options: ['Frankie Says Relax', `Dinosaurs rule`, 'Evolution'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'What did Phoebe call her cross-country trip with Joey?',
    answer: 'A "frienaissance"',
    options: ['A "frienaissance"', 'A "road trip"', 'A "bromance"'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: `What was written on Ross's back when he woke up in Las Vegas?`,
    answer: 'Just Married',
    options: ['Just Married', 'Just Divorced', 'How you doing'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: `What was written on Ross's forehead when he woke up in Las Vegas?`,
    answer: 'Ross',
    options: ['Ross', 'Chandler', 'Joey'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'What term did Ross coin that Chandler tried to use with Janice?',
    answer: 'The "hug and roll"',
    options: ['The "hug and roll"', 'Going Commando', 'Oh, my god'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'What was the name Ross used for "total state of awareness?"',
    answer: 'Unagi',
    options: ['Unagi', 'Going Commando', 'Super Focused'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'What does C.H.E.E.S.E. stand for?',
    answer: 'Computerized Humanoid Electronically Enhanced Secret Enforcer',
    options: ['Computerized Humanoid Electronically Enhanced Secret Enforcer', 'Coming Home Extra Extra Soapy Evenly', 'Come Help Every Egg Still Evolving'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'When Chandler left the country, what address did he give Janice?',
    answer: '15 Yemen Road, Yemen',
    options: ['15 Yemen Road, Yemen', '23 Paris Ave, France', '54 China St. China'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: `Joey has t-shirts made up for Ross's bachelor party. What do they say?`,
    answer: 'Ross Geller Bachelor Bash 1998',
    options: ['Ross Geller Bachelor Bash 1998', 'Ross Geller Taken Again 1998', 'Ross Geller RIP 1998'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'What song did Ross dedicate to Rachel over the radio?',
    answer: 'With or Without You',
    options: ['With or Without You', `I'll be there for you`, 'Baby got back'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: `Act out the alternative gesture Ross invents for "flipping the bird"?`,
    answer: 'Make two fists at someone, and knock the sides of your fists together twice',
    options: ['Make two fists at someone, and knock the sides of your fists together twice', 'Stick out your middle finger', 'Flap your arms like a bird'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'What did Ross not want his tombstone to say',
    answer: 'Ross Geller: Three Divorces',
    options: ['Ross Geller: Three Divorces', 'Ross Geller: Buried Alive', 'Ross Geller: Great Father'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: `How does Ross insult Rachel's Thanksgiving rifle?`,
    answer: 'It tastes like feet!',
    options: ['It tastes like feet!', 'It looks awful!', 'It smells horrible!'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'What loving nickname does Mr. Geller occasionally call Monica?',
    answer: 'Harmonica',
    options: ['Harmonica', 'Pumkin', 'Fatty'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'What does Ross scream when moving his couch?',
    answer: 'PI-VOT',
    options: ['PI-VOT', 'I fell asleep', 'We were on a break'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: `What did Joey say when wearing Chandler's clothes?`,
    answer: 'Could I be wearing anymore clothes',
    options: ['Could I be wearing anymore clothes', 'This is whack', 'Do I look bigger?'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: `Finish this quote: "I don't even have a ____"`,
    answer: 'Plan',
    options: ['Plan', 'Car', 'Boyfriend'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: `What is a "moo point?"`,
    answer: `You know like a cow's opinion. It doesn't matter. It's moo.`,
    options: [`You know like a cow's opinion. It doesn't matter. It's moo.`, 'What a cow is looking at', `When a cow tries to go "boo"`],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: `Fill in the blanks: If it's a girl ____ and if it's a boy ____`,
    answer: 'Phoebe, Pheebo',
    options: ['Phoebe, Pheebo', 'Jim, Janine', 'luke, Leia'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: `Finish this quote: "Thirteen bathrooms in this place and I threw up in the..."`,
    answer: 'Coat closet',
    options: ['Coat closet', 'Bedroom', 'Kitchen'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'What did Phoebe change her name to?',
    answer: 'Princess Consuela Bananahammock',
    options: ['Princess Consuela Bananahammock', 'Crap Bag', 'Regina Flangi'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: `What does Joey respond to this clue?: "It's White"`,
    answer: 'Paper. Snow. A ghost!',
    options: ['Paper. Snow. A ghost!', 'Casper. Wedding dress. Snow White!', 'Light, Ice, Stars!'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'What word does Joey use to sound nineteen?',
    answer: 'Whack',
    options: ['Whack', 'Foshizzle', 'Lame'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: `Who said, "She's your lobster!"?`,
    answer: 'Phoebe',
    options: ['Phoebe', 'Rachel', 'Monica'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'How does Ross defend sleeping with the copy girl?',
    answer: 'We were on a break!',
    options: ['We were on a break!', 'He needed to make a copy', 'He was seduced'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: `What is Ross referring to when he said, "Why is it inside out?"`,
    answer: `Rachel's hairless cat`,
    options: [`Rachel's hairless cat`, 'His pink sweater', 'His leather pants'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'What French sentence can Joey not say?',
    answer: `Je m'appelle Claude`,
    options: [`Je m'appelle Claude`, 'Merci', 'Bonjour'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'What does Monica say when Rachel cuts up all of her credit cards?',
    answer: `Welcome to the real world. It sucks. You're gonna love it!`,
    options: [`Welcome to the real world. It sucks. You're gonna love it!`, 'No more debt', 'Payback'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'What promoted Chandler to say, "Was that place...the sun?"',
    answer: `Ross' mistake at the tanning salon`,
    options: [`Ross' mistake at the tanning salon`, 'When Monica gets stung by the jellyfish', 'When they have a blackout'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'Who said, "The more I drink, the less there is for the kids to drink"?',
    answer: 'Phoebe',
    options: ['Phoebe', 'Monica', 'Rachel'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: `When does Ross say, "You're over me? When were you under me?"`,
    answer: `When he finds Rachel's drunken voicemail`,
    options: [`When he finds Rachel's drunken voicemail`, 'After moving the couch', 'When Carol comes out the closet'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: `Who does Joey say, "You don't own a TV? What's all your furniture pointed at?" to?`,
    answer: `A paleontologist at Ross' convention in the Bahamas`,
    options: [`A paleontologist at Ross' convention in the Bahamas`, 'Charlie', 'The guy hitting on Ross'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'Finish this quote: "Look at her standing there with those yams. My Two greatest enemies, Ross..."?',
    answer: 'Rachel Green and complex carbohydrates',
    options: ['Rachel Green and complex carbohydrates', 'Angelina Jolie and marriage', 'Fatties and calories'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'In your best "Janice" voice, recite her annoying catch phrase',
    answer: 'Oh, my god',
    options: ['Oh, my god', 'Oh, come on', 'Wow really'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'What catch phrase do the Friends use to describe not wearing underwear?',
    answer: 'Going Commando',
    options: ['Going Commando', 'No Undies' , 'Laundry Day'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'What does WENUS stand for?',
    answer: 'Weekly Estimated Net Usage Statements',
    options: ['Weekly Estimated Net Usage Statements', 'Was Extra Negative Using Sheets', 'Why Even Negotiate User Spending'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: `What was Ben's first word?`,
    answer: 'Hi',
    options: ['Hi', 'Asleep', 'Bye'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: `Fill in the black: "____ doesn't share food!"`,
    answer: 'Joey',
    options: ['Joey', 'Chandler', 'Ross'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'When Joey placed an ad for a roommate, what did it say?',
    answer: 'Wanted: female roommate, non-smoker, non-ugly',
    options: ['Wanted: female roommate, non-smoker, non-ugly', 'Wanted: Hot girl', `Wanted: Chandler's replacement`],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'When Joey says, "This is where I win all my money back", what is he referring to?',
    answer: 'The breakfast buffet in Las Vegas',
    options: ['The breakfast buffet in Las Vegas'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: `What song did Rachel sing at Barry and Mindy's wedding?`,
    answer: 'Copacabana',
    options: ['Copacabana', 'Smelly Cat', `I'll be there for you`],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: `What does Rachel want to be referred to as in Joey's Soap Opera Digest Magazine interview?`,
    answer: 'Gal pal Rachel Green',
    options: ['Gal pal Rachel Green', `Joey's girlfriend`, `Joey's bestfriend`],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: `According to a sign in Joey's apartment, what odds does Five-Card Charlie pay?`,
    answer: 'Five-Card Charlie Pays Five to One',
    options: ['Five-Card Charlie Pays Five to One', 'Five-Card Charlie Pays One to Five', 'Five-Card Charlie Pays Five to Five'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'When Joey needs to look 19 for a TV commercial, what does Phoebe say will make him look younger?',
    answer: `[your eyes] give you away. There's just too much wisdom in there. Just put some tea bags on them for like 15 minutes`,
    options: [`[your eyes] give you away. There's just too much wisdom in there. Just put some tea bags on them for like 15 minutes`, 
    'A time machine', 'Going to sleep early that night'],
  },
  {
    category: 'LITERATURE',
    question: 'What does Ross yell at Rachel about her letter?',
    answer: '18 pages, front and back',
    options: ['18 pages, front and back', 'The grammar', 'No stamp on it'],
  }
]